<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>yuge8·专注电影资源分享</title>
  <subtitle>专注电影视频资源分享|请关注yuge8.com</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yuge8.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-07-03T17:42:12.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://yuge8.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>nm4k</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>明天</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ming-tian/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ming-tian/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:42:11.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:42:12.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/83f5449b50468feb8f035fc5a9cbaf0a.png" alt=""><br>[明天]简介：</p>
<p>　　1945年的日本长崎随时有空袭。护士矢惠和工人中川庄治准备结婚，因空袭频繁无法进行结婚典礼，决定拍张结婚照以作纪念。同去拍照的有怀孕的姐姐鹤子和姐姐的同事亚矢。亚矢也怀孕三个月了，情人高谷藤雄被派往中国后，杳无音讯。刚拍完照片，鹤子突然感到阵痛，赶紧请来产婆接生。母亲兹依赶忙煮豆子让她吃。矢惠的妹妹去找在长崎医大学习的男朋友英雄，正碰上英雄收到征召集合令。英雄不愿应征．劝矢惠的妹妹同他一起私奔，被拒绝。在俘虏收容所，一个英国士兵因得不到治疗死了。英雄觉悟到这是对俘虏见死不救的军队。于是这一夜坐立不安，去玩了妓女。庄治和矢惠迎来了新婚第一夜。鹤子也生下一个可爱的男孩。每个人都向往着明天，努力地活下去。8月9日原子弹在长崎上空爆炸。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>There were air raids in Nagasaki, Japan, in 1945. Nurse Hui Hui and worker Nakagawa Shoji prepare to marry, because the air raid is frequent, unable to carry on the wedding ceremony, decided to take a wedding photo as a souvenir. To take pictures of pregnant sister, crane son and sister colleagues, sub - vector. The vector is three months pregnant lover, Takatani Fujio was sent to Chinese, without hearing a word about. Just take a photo, he suddenly felt pain, immediately invited midwife. Mother Ziyi quickly let her eat cooked beans. Hui sister went to study in the rise of Nagasaki Medical University boyfriend hero, just call set to receive a hero. The hero refused to apply. His younger sister eloped with him, and was refused. At the internment camp, a British soldier died because he was not treated. The hero is aware of this is the army captured from ruin. So this night, restless, went to play with prostitutes. Zhuang governance and Yuan Hui ushered in the first night of marriage. Crane son also gave birth to a lovely boy. Everyone is looking forward to tomorrow, and work hard to live. The atomic bomb exploded over Nagasaki in August 9th.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1824356/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1824356/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:659ACF8B8BB73CC7CC3EFD9A34AF7B4E05913BAA" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:659ACF8B8BB73CC7CC3EFD9A34AF7B4E05913BAA</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0FEB35DA1E40C6483CD3046C333588B21EBA19E2" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0FEB35DA1E40C6483CD3046C333588B21EBA19E2</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:036AEACD1CF4A8623A731E0A01CF04CBE0D1E0B8" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:036AEACD1CF4A8623A731E0A01CF04CBE0D1E0B8</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:4A2D1415CAA8EE291F031693092697105EA3EE83" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:4A2D1415CAA8EE291F031693092697105EA3EE83</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:6617301C967D955DECD3F8D69ABC4558207E8BC0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:6617301C967D955DECD3F8D69ABC4558207E8BC0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/83f5449b50468feb8f035fc5a9cbaf0a.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[明天]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　1945年的日本长崎随时有空袭。护士矢惠和工人中川庄治准备结婚，因空袭频繁无法进行结婚典礼，决定拍张结婚照以
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="明天" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%98%8E%E5%A4%A9/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>摇滚舞曲，悄悄地演奏吧</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-yao-gun-wu-qu-%EF%BC%8C-qiao-qiao-di-yan-zou-ba/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-yao-gun-wu-qu-，-qiao-qiao-di-yan-zou-ba/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:42:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:42:01.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/a3df6be9435928b6a525faf695dc8550.png" alt=""><br>[摇滚舞曲，悄悄地演奏吧]简介：</p>
<p>　　高中生片冈俊介的父母离婚后，他和母亲、妹妹，搬到长野县松本市去住。俊介在转入松本新学校前，因米奈、顿达来找碴打架，反而使他们结为好朋友。一天，他们三人看见有几个学生结伙欺侮一个外校的学生，便仗义解救，于是他们四人成了好朋友，一起搞了个爵士乐演奏小组，可总也攒不起钱来。“乡土方言”论文的有奖比赛征集活动的一等奖可获奖金50万日元，于是四人绞尽脑汁，由米奈负责执笔成文。论文被评为银奖，得到30万日元的奖金。盼望已久的乐器到手了。他们立即开始练习，并决定以“克拉依姆演奏小组”的名义公演《安琪儿小夜曲》。不幸，米奈因摩托车事故成了永不回来的人。他们在米奈的遗像前演唱了爵士歌曲。大家随着乐曲默念米奈的音容笑貌。<br>　　影片非常直率地描写了男子汉的友情，可谓是一部豪爽的青春电影，成为年度最受大学生欢迎的作品。影片着重刻画了“男斗呼组”这四个人所扮角色性格的生动特点，把这四个角色演活了。作品尽情地渲染了年青人的友情，充分地渲染后又非常迅速果断地加以节制——一个意外事故袭来，好朋友因摩托车事故，永远不能再回来了。这不仅寓意青春的结束，也寓意了人生的缩影。那就是留在活着的青年人心里的深深的伤痕。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>High school student Kataoka Shunsuke’s parents divorced, he and his mother and sister moved to Nagano Prefecture, Matsumoto city to live. The new school in Shunsuke pine, because Milne, up to Dayton to pick fights, but to make them as good friends. One day, the three of them saw several students Gang bully a school student, so they will save people, four people have become good friends, get together a jazz group, the total can not save money. “The local dialect” the Award contest solicitation will receive a prize of 500 thousand yen, and four brains, Minai into shape by responsible. The paper was awarded Silver Prize and received a prize of 300 thousand yen. The long awaited instruments have arrived. They immediately began to practice, and decided to name “carat Barenboim playing group” Premiere “Angel Serenade”. Unfortunately, Minaiyin motorcycle accident to never come back. They sang jazz songs in the picture of milne. You say the music with Minai voice and expression.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href=""><font color="#1e92fb"></font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0F78E8184A1ED3ACB94B3AECBE8DE5B16A9DC150" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0F78E8184A1ED3ACB94B3AECBE8DE5B16A9DC150</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:AE8DA396D489BBC027FC11E7F03494B8E3040D8E" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:AE8DA396D489BBC027FC11E7F03494B8E3040D8E</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:D83E70E7539C280B4409B0AE0EB0857AAD7A3BDA" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:D83E70E7539C280B4409B0AE0EB0857AAD7A3BDA</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:58510C0B773950EB69A91C6AC6D9279C6AC75D4D" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:58510C0B773950EB69A91C6AC6D9279C6AC75D4D</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C8E4253FE84556010F0E1C12A2E242E2C23A77D6" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C8E4253FE84556010F0E1C12A2E242E2C23A77D6</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/a3df6be9435928b6a525faf695dc8550.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[摇滚舞曲，悄悄地演奏吧]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　高中生片冈俊介的父母离婚后，他和母亲、妹妹，搬到长野县松本市去住。俊介在转入松本新学校前，
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="摇滚舞曲，悄悄地演奏吧" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%91%87%E6%BB%9A%E8%88%9E%E6%9B%B2%EF%BC%8C%E6%82%84%E6%82%84%E5%9C%B0%E6%BC%94%E5%A5%8F%E5%90%A7/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>快盗ルビイ</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-kuai-dao-%E3%83%AB%E3%83%93%E3%82%A4/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-kuai-dao-ルビイ/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:41:45.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:41:45.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/b6638e1e48cb700e0658f3ee64e9ce0f.png" alt=""><br>[快盗ルビイ]简介：</p>
<p>　　ある日DM発送会社に勤める林徹のマンションに女の子が引っ越してきた。彼女は加藤留美というフリーのスタイリストだが、本当はルビイという名の快盗だった。徹はさっそく相棒として犯罪を手伝わされる。まずは巧妙な手口で食料品屋の親父から売上げ金を盗んだが、中味は大金とは程遠くて経費を差し引くと赤字だった。頭の切れるルビイと頼りない徹だったか、二人は次に銀行襲撃を計画した。しかし、これも徹が脅迫の手紙と買物メモを間違えて失敗。ルビイは凝りずに宝石店詐欺を試るが、あっさり店主に見抜かれてしまう。犯罪計画を楽しむような二人は豪華マンションに忍び込むが、管理が厳しくて脱出するのに精一杯で物を盗むどころではなかった。徹はルビイが好きだが、彼女には恋人がいた。ルビイが喧嘩した恋人に宛てた手紙を取り戻してほしいという。徹は気やすく引き受けるが、運悪く警察に捕まってしまう。気のいい刑事の計らいで徹はすぐに釈放されたが、ルビイはそんな自分のワガママを聞き入れてくれた彼を暖かく迎えた。そして今度は徹のほうが、新しい犯罪計画をルビイに持ちかけるのだった。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Aru DM shipment: will Lyncher of Qin in the club, Ma,, in female, after the woman of child lead with the ta. She is studying in the United States last longer, and Kato, of her, and her graduate, do not, and this is when nursing, and the last name of fast and complete nursing after a case of theft. The penetration is flying for national and the environmental crime has been on the team in terms of national hand guys. Ma: wa - hand mouth was a clever food house of father Kara senbai on gold or stolen, the taste is on nursing, and is on the far side of Daikin costs or poor woman on the lead and deficit after nursing for. In terms of cutting head, and the Lai and this last - penetration and two, after nursing for a time in the bank raid or plan hyperplastic. Woman, woman, child, in terms of these projects into shopping and toilet paper and stress between the failure forms of or not. This is the setting, and by fraud or on the gem shop test, and in this we see thou after national owner, the terms provided complete ma. Plan or better or environmental crime by two people: U - Ma,, in luxury, for better management, bear Yu, Yan. On the emergence of a cup on continued to fine or better material was stolen was: CIECC after Ta Na ka. Is good, and the penetration, that is, with importance, as lovers, ICDRG. The sound, and, in the case of hyperplastic lovers or take this Wan toilet paper. At last Ti and live longer. And also, on the penetration is induced by force with, with, on the police to catch the vicious woman after the ~ ~ U. In the last, last of the criminal is still kind of live in the penetration meter in national terms, and put Shi for the division, is for self - cancer of Ma Ma or smell with gas in the case of other terms or terms on the warm welcome, on the forms of ta. For this is the degree of penetration., complete, new environmental plan, or the last crime and in holding force with UTI, after a case of noda.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href=""><font color="#1e92fb"></font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:92D77D9F7974285E22270DE6C21F518F2654D249" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:92D77D9F7974285E22270DE6C21F518F2654D249</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9947C208727B08AE197B3C40B1195C701BC42B83" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9947C208727B08AE197B3C40B1195C701BC42B83</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0E7CF5BF583366A97C8D3EF63751AF6CD004347D" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0E7CF5BF583366A97C8D3EF63751AF6CD004347D</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:2935521A9FF30E3D6026D278ABFCAFBDF0A37E94" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:2935521A9FF30E3D6026D278ABFCAFBDF0A37E94</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:FB2BE98E4BCF7093ED4358761B42BC1BD69F4DA8" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:FB2BE98E4BCF7093ED4358761B42BC1BD69F4DA8</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/b6638e1e48cb700e0658f3ee64e9ce0f.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[快盗ルビイ]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　ある日DM発送会社に勤める林徹のマンションに女の子が引っ越してきた。彼女は加藤留美というフリーのスタイ
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="快盗ルビイ" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E5%BF%AB%E7%9B%97%E3%83%AB%E3%83%93%E3%82%A4/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>凶暴的男人</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-xiong-bao-de-nan-ren/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-xiong-bao-de-nan-ren/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:41:34.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:41:35.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/059a27fc098a2f115debcea36134bed4.png" alt=""><br>[凶暴的男人]简介：</p>
<p>　　作风粗暴的警官我妻谅介（北野武饰）在警匪两界颇具名望，也因此结下不少仇家。在某次追查毒品贩子遇害事件时，顺藤摸瓜查到青年实业家仁藤（岸部一德饰）为幕后指使。同时发现，其警局好友岩城（平泉城饰）亦在毒品犯罪中占据重要位置。然调查才刚展开，岩城即被仁藤麾下杀手（白龙饰）杀害，并伪装成自杀现场。<br>　　杀手清弘为诱我妻上钩，绑架了我妻的智障妹妹（川上麻衣子饰）加以轮暴，并使其沉溺毒品无法自拔。我妻辞去警局职务，持枪向仁藤和清弘展开报复……<br>　　本片为日本喜剧明星北野武的导演处女作。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Rude officer my wife Ryosuke (Takeshi) on two world famous, so many enemies. In a trace drug traffickers killing, Shuntengmogua found young businessman Hitoto (Kishibe Hide ornaments) are behind. Also found that its police friend Rock City (Pingquan city decoration) also occupies an important position in drug-related crime. However, the investigation had just begun, and the city was killed by Hitoto’s killer (white dragon) and disguised as a suicide scene.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1293995/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1293995/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:E0708EB2F75E19DF870F17EE7EDB5E290A77F89B" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:E0708EB2F75E19DF870F17EE7EDB5E290A77F89B</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:33135F7350DBC97B9A0468F9B09FB9E666AE3B48" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:33135F7350DBC97B9A0468F9B09FB9E666AE3B48</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:47EFDF56B0F71858573CAF878F7CB5E370F7E9DE" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:47EFDF56B0F71858573CAF878F7CB5E370F7E9DE</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9B3FABCC2263C7541A40C34222F3D71D31124E7D" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9B3FABCC2263C7541A40C34222F3D71D31124E7D</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:38F1286A2B695431340645D9A10BBF83A458FE8A" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:38F1286A2B695431340645D9A10BBF83A458FE8A</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/059a27fc098a2f115debcea36134bed4.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[凶暴的男人]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　作风粗暴的警官我妻谅介（北野武饰）在警匪两界颇具名望，也因此结下不少仇家。在某次追查毒品贩子遇害事件时
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="凶暴的男人" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E5%87%B6%E6%9A%B4%E7%9A%84%E7%94%B7%E4%BA%BA/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>黑雨</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-hei-yu/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-hei-yu/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:41:19.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:41:21.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/90168ef06203bb1e77f5c811a928739d.png" alt=""><br>[黑雨]简介：</p>
<p>　　1945年，20岁的少女高丸矢须子（田中好子饰）为避战乱，乘船前往叔叔闲间重松（北村和夫饰）家。伴随着刺眼的白光和巨大的爆炸声，来自地狱的黑雨从天而降，须子被迫接受了死神的洗礼。5年后，闲间夫妇将矢须子收为女儿，一家人平静地生活在福山市的小岛村中。原爆给普通民众带来的危害此时已渐渐凸现，受到白光辐射的人们罹患各种病症，正常人对他们敬而远之。亲身经历战争的人也在心中留下巨大创伤，神志错乱，久久无法过回正常生活。美丽的矢须子见证着亲人和朋友所遭受的痛苦和折磨，而最终，战争的幽灵也开始侵蚀她的生命……<br>　　本片根据井伏鱒二的同名小说改编，并荣获1990年日本学院奖最佳作品、最佳摄影、最佳女主角、最佳导演、最佳编剧、最佳剪辑、最佳灯光、最佳配乐和最佳女配角等多项大奖；1989年戛纳电影节天主教人道精神大奖特别提及和技术大奖。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>In 1945, the 20 year old girl Takamaru Yasuko (Tanaka Yoshiko ornaments) to avoid the war, boat to Uncle leisure heavy pine (Kitamura Kazuo ornaments) home. With the dazzling white light and a huge explosion, from hell black whiskers was forced to drop from the clouds, the baptism of death. 5 years later, the couple will receive free between vector suko for her daughter, one family living quietly in Fushan City Island village. The harm caused by the explosion to the ordinary people has gradually become apparent. People suffering from white light radiation suffer from various diseases, and the normal people keep a distance from them. Those who have gone through war have left great scars in their hearts, and they are unable to go back to normal life for a long time. Vector suko beautiful to witness the relatives and friends have suffered pain and suffering, and ultimately, the specter of war also began to erode her life……</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1294867/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1294867/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:275E1814F695F121E1DDCF84AD94E43D483CF63C" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:275E1814F695F121E1DDCF84AD94E43D483CF63C</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5954D8A3603D48501E8FFE4B6589453080B395F7" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5954D8A3603D48501E8FFE4B6589453080B395F7</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F19C6018505C4BEF47EC101902BD01A9CEF7A596" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F19C6018505C4BEF47EC101902BD01A9CEF7A596</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5E5BC1F0FEDA0913B2C780569827FEB98505E347" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5E5BC1F0FEDA0913B2C780569827FEB98505E347</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9EC0CBD22ACB6485F03C062768A916DE94704B04" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9EC0CBD22ACB6485F03C062768A916DE94704B04</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/90168ef06203bb1e77f5c811a928739d.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[黑雨]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　1945年，20岁的少女高丸矢须子（田中好子饰）为避战乱，乘船前往叔叔闲间重松（北村和夫饰）家。伴随着刺眼的
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="黑雨" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E9%BB%91%E9%9B%A8/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>不要口出狂言</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-bu-yao-kou-chu-kuang-yan/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-bu-yao-kou-chu-kuang-yan/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:41:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:41:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/f7e54f992eca539d622500abb6d0f8c6.png" alt=""><br>[不要口出狂言]简介：</p>
<p>　　イーグル友田との試合で負傷し、再起不能となった元チャンピオン、安達英志は、所属のナショナルジムを飛び出して、自らのジムを設立した。ある日、英志のジムにふらりと中年男が現れた。男は左島牧雄という元ウェルター級の日本チャンピオンだった。英志は左島をコーチとして雇うが、ジムに集まった練習生たちは英志のあまりの横暴さに嫌気をさし、みな去ってしまう。結局、ジムを閉めることになった英志は、ナショナルジムに戻り、会長の鴨井とその娘・貴子、そして左島と共に現役カムバックへと向かっていった。そんな時、英志のカムバック戦の相手が決まった。ナショナルジムでの英志の後輩で今は原田ジムにいる清田だった。そして、遂に試合の日となり英志は再びリングに立った。ゴングが鳴り、清田と命賭けの死闘を繰り広げる英志。しかし、前の試合での負傷を背負っている英志にはやはり不利であった。そして、見兼ねた貴子がタオルを投げた瞬間、同時に英志のパンチが清田をダウンさせたのだった。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>And a group, friends of the field trial and was wounded. He cannot, and two yuan for longer after that, and the fields of organization, topics An Daying Chi WA, the system of nano nanomaterials, and fly out. Or: Tokyo, Tokyo and the self CSAC: set up or hyperplastic. Aru Japanese and English records of Tokyo and in this kind of examples and middle-aged male, the terms. Male: Sashima Makio and Hai Yuan,, complete grade Japanese team, now, after that over the fields of topics. En-liang: left Island Studies, and expands the organization or hire, and in Tokyo, complete set of Ma TA ta after practice: en-liang of UTI ~ of violence in this actually national or national environmental rights protection, too, have a go at ~ u after. The ending, and will close in Tokyo by language and in - or after en-liang: nano systems, and in this Ti nano Tokyo, President of wells, the mother duck and method for coding for the son, and is in the form of active left island and back to the master clima fries in and after the last case of flying. For cancer, in the form of Na en-liang and battle of clima fries in hand, will ~ for flying. , Tokyo, nano nano and massively en-liang of generations in Tokyo and now live in Harada Kiyota in nursing after. For the woman, then to try all the day and this is again - en-liang for her, in that stand for flying. , Ming and Qing Tian Group, this life and death of gambling at Hiroshima in this offensive has included en-liang. Woman, woman, before the trial and after the massively wounded or bear in Hai en-liang in Wa Wa, this was actually negative after. For the woman, and for now, son, NE TA TA or throw in at the same time, instant en-liang of pulp, team, or Kiyota, national estate case of Noda after.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1547199/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1547199/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:21476D423B548E054EE68A247247864DCB32DBC8" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:21476D423B548E054EE68A247247864DCB32DBC8</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:A5970DDA9426D0E4A32CB81A72CE3EDC2773EF06" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:A5970DDA9426D0E4A32CB81A72CE3EDC2773EF06</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:309EDB7B441827BEBB756939A83CA6BFA5122F67" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:309EDB7B441827BEBB756939A83CA6BFA5122F67</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5238218632C8976CB8F2A364A57072CF0A5212E0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5238218632C8976CB8F2A364A57072CF0A5212E0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F853637B057DD555CC84A36EE021BC82F876AC4A" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F853637B057DD555CC84A36EE021BC82F876AC4A</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/f7e54f992eca539d622500abb6d0f8c6.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[不要口出狂言]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　イーグル友田との試合で負傷し、再起不能となった元チャンピオン、安達英志は、所属のナショナルジムを飛び
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="不要口出狂言" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E4%B8%8D%E8%A6%81%E5%8F%A3%E5%87%BA%E7%8B%82%E8%A8%80/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>冲绳草莽英雄</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-chong-sheng-cao-mang-ying-xiong/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-chong-sheng-cao-mang-ying-xiong/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:40:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:40:55.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/356f50323248cf7bc8235145b4f2e7e0.png" alt=""><br>[冲绳草莽英雄]简介：</p>
<p>　　1969倚年铱，协冲照绳岛处于美军掉的瓢控呢制蜕下人。路岛姬民遁分屿为渴望灭复归账日哈本术的多馅数派、愿意维炯持现状括和厕主张悦冲绳绚独立幕的两迅个少数窍派。青年基鲁不属于啸任兢何一个第派别肮，他在约西厨原制预糖所工作绑，拳对西韵原巍亲方头的养女你美丽支的麻莱掩一御往情深呀。拯在咬一帛次支偶然事肇件嘿中，膛基鲁得咸知锈麻莱票其实碍是峙一头猪蓄变森的。亲锹方知情后园大剃怒困，举刊枪拇要射酒杀知道真相的赃基鲁约。基逻鲁在怀动龚物占卜师妹市妹蚜的舰帮助贿下，诚逃进运玉森疟林遁。在合那里，葫基昼鲁遇稻到秤了妖实精奇捆基木写纳，被赋予一颗圣石砷，从而织获题得怨了谰超能降力。娥从此幼基买鲁猜成徐了夕一剂名侠田盗，欲他昭偷袭了美军壶的会仓库和半作恶简多粕端的邓日本波动苦物百商淀会瘪。有有人来联系倦他炉请他狮参氛加赠一贾场醒表现基笺鲁英瘩雄事噪迹柒的油话剧揪，夏在鸦演出蓉中价，睫台梨上鸦的基鲁被株亲方用枪击中贬…炊…<br>　　这碴是一部须奇幻咽电影螺。拜故事李发生滑在捆冲酝绳岛回归日本犹的前夕巾，在村当时庚纷土乱夯复涧杂聘的辗局错势命中图，有继一位拥有超罐能煤力峪的民间侠守义砍英莲雄脱泻颖慨而瞪出。探本盐片成侣功嫂地将现毕实造与嘶虚滩幻融湍会胯在耳一起，淌一方面对呻当时的毙社会步状烷况做了猾写寅实地交匙待，同享时痞又让各真种钡拥有挪非现实疤力训量的人挫物粉禄墨登无场唇，然而买在胞特察殊日的街历衍史背镶景癌下衫，人遇物超乍能力影并不显房得响突兀皋，崇反而认成为推知动妊故姨事发展的关固键。给在再影片悲中蓝，仑冲绳烫民间传前说呸中的说猪化身美朱女、灶妖伙精奇逼基倚木纳都有登渣场，人功物呆的猪对话操也揩完矣全饭采用冲绳凤的裕方言，这使本苛片陷显示柑出酗浓影郁动的乡器土气息和地吮方赠文恩化梭风颅格。匀本诫片钦是1989醒年信电一影慢旬报面评出珍的年度十佳呀电影歼之惺一右，在疾国厨际上也广获志赞努誉匝。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>1969 years on iridium, according to co Chong island in the U.S. dropped rope control system under the shed scoop. Lu Ji Min Yu Dun Island divided into longing for the return on the filling account number, to send haben operation status to the toilet and dimensional Jiong advocate Yue Okinawa Xuan independent act two Xun minority faction. Xiao Jing Ren kiru youth does not belong to any one of the factions of his work in the Chuang, tied about western kitchen made of pre sugar, boxing on the West Yun Wei original Pro Square branch of your beautiful daughter Ma Lai to mask a royal wife. To bite a support in silk accident Zhao pieces hey, bore Dexian know Ma Lai Lu rust ticket a pig is actually because of Zhi Sen’s storage change. A large Pro informed backyard shaving anger trapped, lift gun to shoot and kill the thumb print of wine to know the truth Jiluyue. Luo Lu Gong in Huai based dynamic object divination sister ship to help sister city aphid bribe, Cheng youseen fled into the forest to escape malaria. In there, day to meet Hu based Lu rice scale real wood bundle demon Jingqi was given a written acceptance, sacred stone, arsenic, was to blame the problem so woven false super drop force. IO from the young base buy Lu guess into Xu, a night of a name of the field thief, want him to attack the American Army pot warehouse and half evil, Jane more meal end of the Deng, Japan fluctuation bitter things, hundred commercial lake will be deflated. There is someone to contact him and ask him the lion reference atmosphere furnace bonus a field up performance based Jian Lu Jia Ying Da Xiong. Seven oil pulling trace noise in the summer drama, Chengdu show the price of crow, the crow kiru pear ciliary Taiwan was shot in the line of parents down… Cooking…</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1467028/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1467028/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0FFBCF9F225AEE8E10C7944A9681B115665CFE29" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:0FFBCF9F225AEE8E10C7944A9681B115665CFE29</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9CE58C61C3A98D5D83E4DFA07AEFCA8E0A89C200" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9CE58C61C3A98D5D83E4DFA07AEFCA8E0A89C200</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1B3CC11DB7A0B5A60BDC5D90129B093C9FFC771B" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1B3CC11DB7A0B5A60BDC5D90129B093C9FFC771B</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:58A075FCF1D30EF655566C424BF102A76111A382" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:58A075FCF1D30EF655566C424BF102A76111A382</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C2AEF7EAAF26D61CA61D52E3DC081633D2BB29B2" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C2AEF7EAAF26D61CA61D52E3DC081633D2BB29B2</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/356f50323248cf7bc8235145b4f2e7e0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[冲绳草莽英雄]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　1969倚年铱，协冲照绳岛处于美军掉的瓢控呢制蜕下人。路岛姬民遁分屿为渴望灭复归账日哈本术的多馅数派
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="冲绳草莽英雄" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E5%86%B2%E7%BB%B3%E8%8D%89%E8%8E%BD%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>北京的西瓜</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-bei-jing-de-xi-gua/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-bei-jing-de-xi-gua/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:40:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:40:40.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/0680aa0fadaa197919e1c3d52c81567f.png" alt=""><br>[北京的西瓜]简介：</p>
<p>　　在船桥市郊外的蔬菜市场，蔬菜店老板春三认识了中国留学生李中山，才知道原来中国留学生的生活很辛苦，于是决定帮助他们。一开始他只是随便做点好事，后来渐渐升级，连自己的生活也牺牲掉了。学生们都非常敬仰他，叫他“日本爸爸”。但是春三不管买卖的话，老婆美智的负担就加重了，结果商店和家庭都出现了危机。“能让商店就这么垮掉么？”留学生们决定帮店里干活。春三和美智流下了感动的泪水。几年后，回到中国的李中山从北京打来一个国际电话，邀请春三和美智访问中国。<br>　　影片根据真实故事改编，温馨幽默，生动展现了日本小镇郊区的生活和小人物的喜怒哀乐，表达了中日友谊。为了让场景生动真实，导演经常设置几人在一起说话的情景，话题又往往不同，语言不通的观众或许会对字幕感到眼花缭乱。导演大林宣彦是日本80年代新电影的重要导演之一，在《电影旬报》评选的80年代十大最佳导演中与铃木清顺、黑泽明并列第七。本片获1989年《电影旬报》十佳奖第六名。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>In the vegetable market on the outskirts of the city bridge, three spring vegetable shop owner met Chinese students Li Zhongshan, Chinese students know that life is very hard, so I decided to help them. At first he was just doing something good, and later he grew up and died. The students all looked up to him and called him “Japanese father””. But in spring three, the burden on the wife and the wise woman increased, regardless of the sale. As a result, there was a crisis in the shops and families. “Will the store collapse?”” The students decided to help the shop. Spring three and wisdom shed the moving tears. A few years later, Li Zhongshan returned to China and made an international call from Beijing, inviting Chun three and Ji chi to visit china.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1401174/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1401174/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:DC398D552C29524B2B3C38B99BD68238328E9A25" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:DC398D552C29524B2B3C38B99BD68238328E9A25</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:FAAB8F06A39CD124D245A520D4700F60733F0E6E" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:FAAB8F06A39CD124D245A520D4700F60733F0E6E</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8D6774D5C63F9ED8DC3381D0ECD7B0B30B90180C" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8D6774D5C63F9ED8DC3381D0ECD7B0B30B90180C</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B120A36F00886049C34CE2336A4C6810178008A0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B120A36F00886049C34CE2336A4C6810178008A0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8928D424E804591413597625F9DF9377B072E091" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8928D424E804591413597625F9DF9377B072E091</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/0680aa0fadaa197919e1c3d52c81567f.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[北京的西瓜]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　在船桥市郊外的蔬菜市场，蔬菜店老板春三认识了中国留学生李中山，才知道原来中国留学生的生活很辛苦，于是决
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="北京的西瓜" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E5%8C%97%E4%BA%AC%E7%9A%84%E8%A5%BF%E7%93%9C/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>利休</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-li-xiu/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-li-xiu/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:40:27.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/fc388479056c450ee179ff288b6a019c.png" alt=""><br>[利休]简介：</p>
<p>　　织田信长被明智光秀刺杀身亡数年后，伺候他的利休当上了信长的继承者丰臣秀吉的茶道首领。利休通过茶水的魅力，笼络了全国的武将，并尽其奢侈，营造了茶道最高府第，京都待庵。即侍候丰臣秀吉的主持僧侣的行宫。构筑了一个利休自己的世界。可是，美梦不长，自石田三成的势力增强以后，秀吉和利休的关系开始出现了激烈的矛盾。起初，利休心爱的徒弟宗二，因冒犯秀吉，被赶出行宫，杀了头。接着，石田三成向秀吉进谗言说“利休对出征朝鲜抱有怀疑”。正巧这时，利休在茶室见到秀吉，不慎谈到出兵朝鲜的事，更加激怒了秀吉。秀吉终于下了一道命令，令利休退出京都，并将他禁闭于大庭院。丰臣秀吉的妻子北政所给利休的妻子利木写了封信，说是利休如果肯认错，她想去乞求秀吉原谅利休。可是，利木的回信只是郑重其事地表示了感谢之外，没说别的事。丰臣秀吉见此信更加生气，命令利休剖腹谢罪。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Oda Nobunaga was a wise light show was assassinated a few years later, his servants and Xiudang on Nobunaga’s successor Toyotomi Hideyoshi tea leader. The tea Rikyu charm, win over the generals, as well as its luxury, a tea ceremony hall to be highest, Kyoto temple. A monastery for monks who serve Toyotomi Hideyoshi. To build a world of their own rikyu. However, it is not long since the Ishida Minari force, and the relationship between Hideyoshi began to appear Rikyu fierce contradiction. At first, the beloved disciple Rikyu two, because I was driven out of the palace, Hideyoshi, killed the head. Then, Ishida Minari to say “Kyrgyzstan into calumny Rikyu suspicious of the Korean battle”. Just then, see in the teahouse Rikyu Hideyoshi, accidentally said North Korean troops do more angered hideyoshi. Hideyoshi finally had an order, so that he will leave the Kyoto Rikyu, and confinement in a large courtyard. Toyotomi Hideyoshi’s wife Beizhengsuo wrote a letter to his wife Lee Rikyu said, if she wants to admit to Rikyu, to beg for forgiveness Hideyoshi rikyu. But, just reply were seriously thanked, did not say anything. Toyotomi Hideyoshi see this letter more angry, ordered Rikyu laparotomy apology.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1293703/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1293703/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:66E5332AB457E22C966683C80A87BA6B317EFD64" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:66E5332AB457E22C966683C80A87BA6B317EFD64</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:277C2610C0DB4CF4862D32539DBA227D9FA5A375" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:277C2610C0DB4CF4862D32539DBA227D9FA5A375</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:CDAC768E9D92BD1509673D7D9EC48EB0007D4AC0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:CDAC768E9D92BD1509673D7D9EC48EB0007D4AC0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B65F9313E08F9A5C3731BFE8D22594CF7014CE00" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B65F9313E08F9A5C3731BFE8D22594CF7014CE00</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:2A82BE41D736F0F801FB8D328436219508745FBA" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:2A82BE41D736F0F801FB8D328436219508745FBA</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：<br><a href="https://yun.baidu.com/pcloud/album/info?uk=1177607424&amp;album_id=8457071273525242546" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">https://yun.baidu.com/pcloud/album/info?uk=1177607424&amp;album_id=8457071273525242546</font></a></p>
<hr>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/fc388479056c450ee179ff288b6a019c.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[利休]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　织田信长被明智光秀刺杀身亡数年后，伺候他的利休当上了信长的继承者丰臣秀吉的茶道首领。利休通过茶水的魅力，笼络
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="利休" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E5%88%A9%E4%BC%91/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>情义知多少</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-qing-yi-zhi-duo-shao/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-qing-yi-zhi-duo-shao/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:40:15.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:40:16.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/abd834dca4368f7e0959e16437904b32.png" alt=""><br>[情义知多少]简介：</p>
<p>　　有钱的门仓常造访地位低微的水田，对其妻子阿民关怀备至；阿民也处处为门仓著想。水田深谙友人心事，只一笑置之。一天，门仓改变以往和蔼态度，在酒会上对老朋友冷嘲热讽，当众奚落水田。水田怒气冲冲，挥袖离去。门仓失去挚友，仍尽力为水田女儿里子撮合恋情。那刻，阿民绽放笑容，因为，门仓早已融入水田家，不能分离……</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Kadokura rich visited humble paddy field, his wife Wang to show the utmost solicitude; Wang also everywhere for the door to the warehouse. Well versed in paddy field friends worry, only laugh. One day, the barn changed its former friendly attitude, sneering at old friends at the cocktail party and taunting paddy fields in public. The paddy field was angry and the sleeves were removed. Door warehouse lost friends, still try to make friends in the paddy field daughter lining. At the moment, O people smile, because the door was already in the water, bin Tian, can not be separated……</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1308551/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1308551/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:07FEAFED9B4835234E3BDABD3277D08CB75C4451" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:07FEAFED9B4835234E3BDABD3277D08CB75C4451</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8CE2289BEE89786BC73F962B862E2F99BC647E5C" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8CE2289BEE89786BC73F962B862E2F99BC647E5C</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:59B98B6411017136A1E5482CB3D978FB8A2E8177" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:59B98B6411017136A1E5482CB3D978FB8A2E8177</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9B1C4500337C40104D64FD5AE3E72CF55572C368" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:9B1C4500337C40104D64FD5AE3E72CF55572C368</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:ECB7EB926939A7C26B76F85A5F9D5FA1BF73D4D3" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:ECB7EB926939A7C26B76F85A5F9D5FA1BF73D4D3</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/abd834dca4368f7e0959e16437904b32.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[情义知多少]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　有钱的门仓常造访地位低微的水田，对其妻子阿民关怀备至；阿民也处处为门仓著想。水田深谙友人心事，只一笑置
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="情义知多少" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%83%85%E4%B9%89%E7%9F%A5%E5%A4%9A%E5%B0%91/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>社葬</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-she-zang/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-she-zang/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:40:02.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:40:02.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/8998e06e003e461d5b9e9beedc77217a.png" alt=""><br>[社葬]简介：</p>
<p>　　太阳报社领导层发生了会长派与社长派之间的权力之争。会长派以太田垣为首，社长派以冈部宪介为首。营业部长赞尾身为冈部派的理事，又受过太垣派的恩情，取中立立场。太田垣因投票被解除职务受刺激被送进医院，社长派为胜利而自豪。而冈部却就在这天晚上，死在艺妓床上。鹫尾又被叫去处理丧事。在治丧委员里为选举社长引起场纠纷。第二天，太田垣复职，并任社葬治丧委员会委员长。鹫尾任执行委员。新闻报导被抹掉。社长选举不了了之。由冈部宪介的死，社长派变成了劣势，太田垣要赞尾自动辞职，鹫尾拒绝了。并以要将内幕斗争泄露给宣传媒介为由威胁太田垣不能将他辞职。社葬那天，治丧委员会会长太田垣宣布的新社长名字却是冈部宪介的儿子冈部恭介。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>The leadership of the Sun newspaper has a dispute over the power between the president and the president. The president is led by the blue earth wall, and the president is headed by Okabe Xiansuke. Sales minister praised the tail as the director of the gang faction, but also received the kindness of the yuan faction, take a neutral position. Tai Yuan Yuan was relieved of the vote and was sent to hospital, and the president was proud of his victory. But the gang died on the geisha bed that night. Revealle has been called to deal with the funeral. Cause the dispute for the election of president in the funeral Committee. The second day, otagaki reinstated, and served as a member agency funeral funeral Committee long. Revealle executive committee. The news was erased. Presidential elections come to nothing. By the death of Okabe Xiansuke, President of school becomes a disadvantage, otagaki to praise the tail to resign, Washio refused. And he could not resign from the threat of leaking insider fighting to propaganda media. She was buried that day, the funeral Committee President Otagaki announced the new name was the son of Okabe Xiansuke Okabe Kyousuke president.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/4034263/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/4034263/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:78355D01BD18B73FAD486B45F42AAD9535DD28E1" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:78355D01BD18B73FAD486B45F42AAD9535DD28E1</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:869DDCDE9BC43B12223A86B1BCC043E8F93597AE" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:869DDCDE9BC43B12223A86B1BCC043E8F93597AE</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:80126CFE7EEB85752372868CF5C5C8D6610BA4C0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:80126CFE7EEB85752372868CF5C5C8D6610BA4C0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:39FEC612DD5F87DF662936E7C9AA0BFB770B2188" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:39FEC612DD5F87DF662936E7C9AA0BFB770B2188</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8A7693EDA88F14D1BDC71BC634404948145E59FA" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8A7693EDA88F14D1BDC71BC634404948145E59FA</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/8998e06e003e461d5b9e9beedc77217a.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[社葬]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　太阳报社领导层发生了会长派与社长派之间的权力之争。会长派以太田垣为首，社长派以冈部宪介为首。营业部长赞尾身为
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="社葬" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E7%A4%BE%E8%91%AC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>千利休：本觉坊遗文</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-qian-li-xiu-%EF%BC%9A-ben-jue-fang-yi-wen/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-qian-li-xiu-：-ben-jue-fang-yi-wen/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:39:48.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:39:49.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/ccb6d8383d34d25044a576c50ff8d965.png" alt=""><br>[千利休：本觉坊遗文]简介：</p>
<p>　　千利休が太閤秀吉の命で自刃してから27年後、愛弟子だった本覺坊は心の師と語らうのみの生活を送っていた。ある日本覺坊は、利休がなぜ秀吉の怒りを買って死んだのか、理由を解明しようと情熱を傾ける織田有楽斎に会って感動を覚えた。そして一年後、本覺坊は有楽斎に、利休の晩年山崎の妙喜庵で催された真夜中の茶会について話した。客は秀吉と、後に小田原落城で秀吉に刃向かって切腹した山上宗二だったが、もう一人がわからなかった。さらに一年後、有楽斎は残る客の一人は利休の弟子の古田織部だと見抜いた。織部も大坂夏の陣で豊臣方に内通したかどで、利休や山上宗二と共に自刃したが、実は三人とも死を誓い合っていた。翌年有楽斎は体が弱り危篤となったが、なお利休の最期の心境を知りたがっていた。本覺坊は夢にみた利休と秀吉の最期の茶事の光景を語り始めた。秀吉は一時の感情で下した利休に対する切腹の命を取り消したが、利休は茶人として守らなければならない砦のために切腹すると言い切った。本覺坊の話が利休の切腹に及ぼうとするところで、有楽斎はもうろうとした意識の中で刃を取って切腹したのだった。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>The life was too, thousands Hideyoshi Kara edge. But since 27 years later, the love for nursing after Fang is one disciple of the heart and language of kind of complete division of life after the group sent to construct ICDRG. Aru: Japan Jue Fang, Na Hideyoshi of Rikyu after the death of this anger or buy, or as the reason of cancer nursing. Yo u understand and love hot or tilting force with ODA Youle Zhai: after the move, or will forms. For the woman after a year, is a music Zhai in self Fang, in later years, Yamazaki Taehee de Hugh urged national terms for really the night of tea in the hyperplastic feeling sweet words. The guest is in Oda Haraochikixiuyoshi, and after Hideyoshi on the edge, to the mountains after seppuku hyperplastic two cases, after nursing for a complete one, guys, moo Kara Na Ka after. We have a kind of national music in the guest of Zhai residual after one year, one is in the Gutianzhibu nursing and disciple Hugh provided ICDRG: see. The weaving of array in Osaka moo Xia Chen Fang in Toyohashi in hyperplastic, De, hill two, Rikyu and CO in hyperplastic, and, since the edge is three people dead or live together and moo ICDRG: after the oath. In the next year or Zhai is weak, and this critical body - for - and, after, in the period of mood or make known this case, after the ICDRG. Fang: in case of self dream to construct in the period of Hideyoshi and make the tea things in this case will start it or language. A moment of feeling was under his control in hyperplastic Rikyu on continued life or take this elimination of seppuku, hyperplastic, and keep the tea is Rikyu. Ra - ra - Hai - Speech at terms of Zhai tameni hara-kiri on continued and cut after last words. One of you, in the workshop and complete in hara-kiri Hugh and was in on continued and, after taking the ritual of Noda was hyperplastic after TA or Zhai is complete or edge of child u and hyperplastic consciousness of.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1299985/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1299985/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:277C2610C0DB4CF4862D32539DBA227D9FA5A375" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:277C2610C0DB4CF4862D32539DBA227D9FA5A375</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:CDAC768E9D92BD1509673D7D9EC48EB0007D4AC0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:CDAC768E9D92BD1509673D7D9EC48EB0007D4AC0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F3A7DD03EAF2A070BE746DF55D617BFC4E409841" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F3A7DD03EAF2A070BE746DF55D617BFC4E409841</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8EA4AC39363AF536B07006C5F9C7BF5ECDD6FCC6" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8EA4AC39363AF536B07006C5F9C7BF5ECDD6FCC6</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1727F80AA33AA1A3E20317CEC2A0D5B327B12D2C" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1727F80AA33AA1A3E20317CEC2A0D5B327B12D2C</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/ccb6d8383d34d25044a576c50ff8d965.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[千利休：本觉坊遗文]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　千利休が太閤秀吉の命で自刃してから27年後、愛弟子だった本覺坊は心の師と語らうのみの生活を送っ
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="千利休：本觉坊遗文" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E5%8D%83%E5%88%A9%E4%BC%91%EF%BC%9A%E6%9C%AC%E8%A7%89%E5%9D%8A%E9%81%97%E6%96%87/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>鸫</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-dong/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-dong/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:39:34.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:39:35.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/561977317714f14f4d68b56234f35bde.png" alt=""><br>[鸫]简介：</p>
<p>　　鸫是一名十八岁的少女，自幼体弱多病，在家人的宠爱呵护中长大。表亲玛利亚从小和鸫一起长大，两人的感情一直很好。在东京读大学的玛利亚，接受了鸫与其姐阳子的邀请前往西伊豆度暑假。一个在美术馆工作名叫恭一的青年突然闯进了她们三人平静的生活，鸫爱上了恭一。而一群暗恋鸫的不良少年伺机将恭一痛打了一顿，继而又杀死了鸫的爱犬。鸫为了报复用尽气力挖了一个大坑作为陷阱，自己因此病倒。假期结束返回东京的玛利亚收到了鸫的一封信，内容仿佛遗书一般。无比担心的玛利亚立刻打电话给鸫，而听筒里却传来了让她深感意外的声音……</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Thrush is a eighteen year old girl, from childhood sickly, in the family’s favorite care grew up. Cousin Maria grew up with a thrush, and the two have always been in a good mood. Maria college in Tokyo, received a thrush’s invitation to the West with its sister Yoko Izu summer vacation. A young man named Christine in the art museum suddenly broke into a peaceful life for the three of them, and the blackbird fell in love with christine. And a group of bad boys who love the thrush will have a good beat, and then kill the thrush’s dog. Thrush in order to revenge exhausted power, dug a pit as a trap, so he fell ill. Maria, who returned to Tokyo at the end of the holiday, received a letter from the thrush as if it were a suicide note. Maria, who was so worried, called the thrush at once, but the receiver heard a surprise……</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1302949/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1302949/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:4817594617EC71AA362A65D721F5F0CF8D7F9779" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:4817594617EC71AA362A65D721F5F0CF8D7F9779</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:BAB44B8286B7CBD11D735231874D5B2B2E3E39BE" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:BAB44B8286B7CBD11D735231874D5B2B2E3E39BE</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:6B2A9BF1EA3DDDA1A3381D6B367C28A4ED5115C4" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:6B2A9BF1EA3DDDA1A3381D6B367C28A4ED5115C4</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:DAA08FD99EA0EA05DBF63F6939A88AED39F3D41D" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:DAA08FD99EA0EA05DBF63F6939A88AED39F3D41D</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:D15522BA1FD71A0CBB6CEACFF07CBBF2E293BDC7" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:D15522BA1FD71A0CBB6CEACFF07CBBF2E293BDC7</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/561977317714f14f4d68b56234f35bde.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[鸫]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　鸫是一名十八岁的少女，自幼体弱多病，在家人的宠爱呵护中长大。表亲玛利亚从小和鸫一起长大，两人的感情一直很好。在
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="鸫" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E9%B8%AB/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>3-4X10月</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-3-4X10-yue/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-3-4X10-yue/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:39:22.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:39:23.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/bf0d3a27d74223f69d86933cfb182162.png" alt=""><br>[3-4X10月]简介：</p>
<p>　　雅树（小野昌彦饰）性格孤僻，难于沟通，在棒球队中不懂配合，即使输掉比赛也如同什么事没发生过一样。某日在加油站打工时，雅树与黑帮大友组成员金井（小泽仁志饰）发生矛盾，金井假装手臂骨折，索取巨额赔偿。Incruz酒吧老板是雅树所在球队的球迷，也曾是大友组成员。他代球队前去交涉，未果。<br>　　雅树等人为对抗黑帮，前往冲绳购买武器。在那里偶遇因挥霍组里资金而被殴打的小混混上原（北野武饰），几人恳求其搞来武器，后者正为资金发愁，欣然同意。<br>　　得到武器的雅树一众回到东京，开始对大友组的报复，他们最终能否成功？</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Elegant tree (Ono Masahiko ornaments) eccentric personality, difficult to communicate, in the baseball team does not know how to match, even if lost the game, as if nothing had happened. One day, when working in the gas station, Ya tree and gangster friends group gold wells (Ozawa Hitoshi ornaments) contradictions, Jin Jing pretend arm fracture, ask for huge compensation. The Incruz bar owner is a fan of the team and a former member of the group. He went to the team to negotiate, but failed.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1297290/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1297290/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C46EDEDD3AEC451BF6CED8EB5BD704F0443FB47C" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C46EDEDD3AEC451BF6CED8EB5BD704F0443FB47C</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:523411A77FB25813407B392DC72BEF5CDF5A281E" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:523411A77FB25813407B392DC72BEF5CDF5A281E</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:2136AF19EDE68ACA3478439C7A59B4287053C1A0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:2136AF19EDE68ACA3478439C7A59B4287053C1A0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F034E701C9A12602A8E68393C19965982B865292" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F034E701C9A12602A8E68393C19965982B865292</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:263740756C2EE38933323B874E5C80D76F1C0685" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:263740756C2EE38933323B874E5C80D76F1C0685</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/bf0d3a27d74223f69d86933cfb182162.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[3-4X10月]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　雅树（小野昌彦饰）性格孤僻，难于沟通，在棒球队中不懂配合，即使输掉比赛也如同什么事没发生过一样。某
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="3-4X10月" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/3-4X10%E6%9C%88/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>洁白的手</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ji-bai-de-shou/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ji-bai-de-shou/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:39:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:39:04.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/8c26df57c9271c2a1b0d2c12177bd9ed.png" alt=""><br>[洁白的手]简介：</p>
<p>　　从东京转学来的松井被安排在五年级3班。这个腼腆的男孩在到学校的第一天便被淘气的同学欺负。同学们发现松井被欺负后竟然拉了裤子，于是对松井更加疏远。孩子们边跑边给松井起着外号，松井郁郁寡欢地回了家。<br>　　<br>　　松井的妈妈找到了同学阿盛的家，她告诉阿盛松井有大小便失禁的病，希望阿盛可以和松井成为好朋友，多多照顾他。阿盛心中虽不情愿，但面对松井妈妈的恳求，他还是勉强答应了。为了不让同学看到自己和松井成为了朋友，阿盛在上学的路上总是和松井保持着距离。<br>　　<br>　　要想被同学接受，松井就必须向大家证明自己的勇气。松井坐上了工地里的矿车，在冲向大海的一瞬间他镇静自若，同学们都开始对松井刮目相看。<br>　　<br>　　一天在上学的路上，松井和阿盛看到一户人家的窗口里伸出一只手。阿盛告诉松井，这一定是一个生病孩子的手，只有在天气好的时候它才会伸出来感受阳光。松井突然对这个伸出手的孩子有种同病相怜的感觉。恰好老师留下了给一个朋友写一封信的作业，松井决定就把这封信写给这个孩子。<br>　　<br>　　阿盛爬到窗口为松井送信，他发现躺在床上的这个生病的女孩竟如此美丽可爱。女孩看过信后给松井回信告诉她自己叫小晶慧，多年来一直生病卧床。松井和阿盛从此对小晶慧更加关注。他们经常会在小晶慧的窗下驻足，松井更是会为她吹起口琴。<br>　　<br>　　但时间不长小晶慧就住到了医院。在阿盛的帮助下，松井爬到树上第一次亲眼看到了小晶慧的样子。遗憾的是几天后老师告诉他们，小晶慧已经离开了这个世界。情窦初开的松井和阿盛都为失去了这样一个好女孩感到悲伤不已。<br>　　<br>　　新的学年开始了，松井因为爸爸工作调动的原因又要转学了。虽然他和同学们相处的时间不长，但在他的童年里，已经深深烙印上了阿盛和那些同学们，当然还有已经在天堂里的小晶慧。<br>　　<br>　　精彩视点：<br>　　<br>　　本片讲述了一个发生在一群情窦初开的男孩子身边的故事，由日本知名导演神山征二郎执导。神山征二郎1971年以儿童电影《鲤鱼之村》登上影坛，1987年的作品《八公物语》成为大热电影。除文艺电影外，他还大力推动平民电影的发展，有《樱花》、《夏天的月光》等多部作品。从影至今，神山拍摄的电影已达23部之多。<br>　　<br>　　本片的女主角南野阳子是日本八、九十年代最当红的女演员之一，被称为“传说中的偶像”。她曾主演过《千年之恋》、《新干线97恋爱物语》、《隔世情未了》等电影和电视剧集，此外她还是一名出色的歌手。在本片中南野阳子的表演入木三分，她将一名清纯俏丽又害羞的年轻老师，对于来自负心男友伤害时的痛苦和面对青春期学生们的尴尬表现得淋漓尽致。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Transfer from Tokyo to Matsui was arranged in the fifth grade class 3. The shy boy was bullied by his naughty classmates on the first day of school. Students found that Matsui was bullied even after pulling pants, and therefore more alienated matsui. The children ran to Matsui, nicknamed “Matsui”, Matsui unhappy home.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1950425/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1950425/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:215E41D15C984C75F4FEEB0A84DA2047AA61CD89" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:215E41D15C984C75F4FEEB0A84DA2047AA61CD89</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:BABB3404D220C4A570BDFE34CE6F81CCCE9DCC66" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:BABB3404D220C4A570BDFE34CE6F81CCCE9DCC66</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:EC968A4EC0864259C2B709E81B3FF22D35EEE784" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:EC968A4EC0864259C2B709E81B3FF22D35EEE784</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:79D20AE516EF57EEBC4091D0ACE5490E1A63C43F" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:79D20AE516EF57EEBC4091D0ACE5490E1A63C43F</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B9B73B10E226DFB99324789BBCDFC28507D021B6" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B9B73B10E226DFB99324789BBCDFC28507D021B6</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/8c26df57c9271c2a1b0d2c12177bd9ed.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[洁白的手]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　从东京转学来的松井被安排在五年级3班。这个腼腆的男孩在到学校的第一天便被淘气的同学欺负。同学们发现松井被
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="洁白的手" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%B4%81%E7%99%BD%E7%9A%84%E6%89%8B/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>等待出击</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-deng-dai-chu-ji/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-deng-dai-chu-ji/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:38:52.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:38:52.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/e8d08b82f85bbb95ea375fdd35762e41.png" alt=""><br>[等待出击]简介：</p>
<p>　　新宿・歌舞伎町。スナック“カシュカシュ”のマスター郷田克彦の前に、ヤクザに追われている女が現れる。女の名はヤン・メイラン、台湾人である。その頃、外では桜道会系戸井田組々長が銃殺される事件が発生し、新宿署のマル暴刑事・軍司が捜査を開始していた。殺人現場にはVHS-Cビデオのアダプターが残されていたが中身のテープはなかった。一方“カシュカシュ”では20年間続いたこの店の閉店パーティが行われており、克彦のかつての全共闘の同志である季律子、秋川、三宅らが集っていた。中にはメイランの姿も見え、実は彼女がベトナム難民であり、偽造パスポートを持つ密国入者であることが判明する。逃走のためのパスポートを取りに店を出たメイランは、戸井田組に追われるが克彦はそんな彼女を救出するのだった。一方、事件を追う軍司は、戸井田組がタイの女にパスポートをネタに売春させ、その女に組長が殺されたらしいことと、女がビデオテープを持っていることをつきとめた。時を同じくして香港ヤクザが戸井田組々員を殺害する事件が起り、そこで軍司はビデオテープを発見する。それは桜道会桜田のフィリピン女の殺人シーンだった。メイランは克彦と仲間に戸井田に脅され、犯されそうになった時、銃が暴発して戸井田を殺してしまったことを打ち明ける。そして対策を練っていた時、秋川が香港ヤクザに殺されてしまい、メイランもさらわれてしまう。克彦は一人でメイランを救出することを決意する。そんな克彦と行動を共にする季律子。リボルバーを手に香港ヤクザのいるフィリピンパブへ向う二人は、ヤクザと警察を向うに激しい銃撃戦の末、メイランを無事逃がす。そして、負傷した二人は互いを支え合いながら薄れかける意識の中で笑い合うのだった。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>Shinjuku and kabuki. That is, the form of “nano fries in the form of” fierce, fierce, Ma, given before, in of Tian Katsuhiko in “chasing guys in terms at last. Now, in terms of female. The name is, female, and I, lumira, Taiwan de aru. For the Ares, Sakura Road: CIECC will at the group has long barrelled kill, in terms of development and national events, and Environmental Department of CAS, Shinjuku Junsi, and violent criminal investigation begins at ICDRG:. The murder scene in the design of VHS-C is that, Communication Institute, the national, the residual terms, in the body of te ICDRG: wa Na Ka ta after a few. A “Dhaka, Dhaka, fierce fierce”: CIECC ICDRG: 20 years of start was closed shop, department store: so, for pulp, and the guys made me cry much of the feeling of Yan g, were full of offensive Comrade De ARU ritsuko, Sichuan, autumn season three, after the house becomes set ICDRG. In the media, and in a lumira appearance, that is, to see the child forms, and refugees in Japanese Vespa nanomaterials, this actually forged pulp, do not hold, or analysis of Genesis in dense in de Aru, language and judge on continued. In the case of escape of pulp, genesis, human will take this as a store or by TA and RA, and is at the group in chasing guys in terms, is for her - Katsuhiko’s been rescued on continued after a case of noda. A party or event, in our school, after u is the group, and Institute of female in the pulp, or into the Institute in genesis, distribution of national estate, for the spring of female leader, killed in national terms for RA. Last, female, and language and the data only a few or a flying at te Che in the language and by analysis with and will. When the woman has the same on Hongkong “, in’s group has been the member of this event, which killed on continued, was in the army for our data is only a few o Te on continued development. For terms: Sakura Cherry field, so the road will leak, murder, and female topics of importance for flying. And I, lumira is Katsuhiko and in school in the national mine Nakama threat, make national terms for longer terms, for in - after, violence, the woman’s gun or kill the woman. The ~ after: language and by force with UTI ming. The Countermeasures for environmental or practice after the ICDRG: when Akigawa, Hongkong in “in national terms. At last kill Ma, and lumira, member of the national terms. The child becomes ~ U guys. A man was a member of the G Yan Wa and lumira, has rescued on continued language and on continued or determined. For cancer - Katsuhiko and action on continued season in total or sub law. Her, or hand in Hongkong, clima in “live in, so in her back to complete topics, and pulp two people:” in and police or to complete. In last gun hit war of shock, and at the end of lumira, and nothing, or fled here. For the woman, two people wounded hyperplastic is sweet or sweet and forms of mutual support, to have a kind of thin terms, force with consciousness of the last laugh in was a complete combination of Noda after.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href=""><font color="#1e92fb"></font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C7EC97751C759FFE1069B4E393BC381DA56A3C6A" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C7EC97751C759FFE1069B4E393BC381DA56A3C6A</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F756FFA6435999F6636927EF0E4156AACA8E51C0" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F756FFA6435999F6636927EF0E4156AACA8E51C0</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:E4F43BCBEBAA9DE1FE35CE728F47FD0CD588C1BF" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:E4F43BCBEBAA9DE1FE35CE728F47FD0CD588C1BF</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:416C69EA2B003E6F589B8369BA137E4E30161392" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:416C69EA2B003E6F589B8369BA137E4E30161392</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1DD1C3FCDF28FDE6FD88DCD53DB82E0751EE38BF" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1DD1C3FCDF28FDE6FD88DCD53DB82E0751EE38BF</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：<br><a href="https://yun.baidu.com/pcloud/album/info?uk=155949893&amp;album_id=6335383931637576020" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">https://yun.baidu.com/pcloud/album/info?uk=155949893&amp;album_id=6335383931637576020</font></a></p>
<hr>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/e8d08b82f85bbb95ea375fdd35762e41.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[等待出击]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　新宿・歌舞伎町。スナック“カシュカシュ”のマスター郷田克彦の前に、ヤクザに追われている女が現れる。女の名
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="等待出击" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E7%AD%89%E5%BE%85%E5%87%BA%E5%87%BB/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>笨金鱼</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ben-jin-yu/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ben-jin-yu/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:38:41.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:38:42.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/d5ac80d7d48e0f3c0c754eaf18067bdc.png" alt=""><br>[笨金鱼]简介：</p>
<p>　　高中生阿薰在一次放学后偶然看到了学校游泳池边的园子，对她一见钟情。也不管自己是个旱鸭子，阿薰当即加入了游泳部。园子对他根本不感兴趣，阿薰却并不放弃，借了辆自行车，每天早上都去接园子上学。渐渐地，园子的母亲也接受了阿薰，这令园子十分恼怒。阿薰为了让园子接受自己，每天拼命练习游泳。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>High school student smoked one after school, accidentally saw the school swimming pool garden, fell in love with her at first sight. No matter he is a HanYaZi, ah Hoon immediately joined the swimming department. The garden was not interested in him at all, but he did not give up. He borrowed a bicycle and went to pick up the garden every morning. Gradually, the mother of the garden accepted the smoke, which made the garden very angry. In order to let the garden accept himself, smoked every day desperately practice swimming.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/3075926/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/3075926/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:08F35FDBAE53D7F712F69173E0A0685D0EF746A3" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:08F35FDBAE53D7F712F69173E0A0685D0EF746A3</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8B7521F3CC7DD1695560CFC878B4B9F113328D23" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8B7521F3CC7DD1695560CFC878B4B9F113328D23</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:A91E8C00B77A7577E26202BB3C43D950A1739A5B" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:A91E8C00B77A7577E26202BB3C43D950A1739A5B</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B9A64670B19E2ED60004AC6BF26CC1716401A34E" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:B9A64670B19E2ED60004AC6BF26CC1716401A34E</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:DED7A56097BD213779A5A289454F6F65D23CA54E" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:DED7A56097BD213779A5A289454F6F65D23CA54E</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/d5ac80d7d48e0f3c0c754eaf18067bdc.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[笨金鱼]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　高中生阿薰在一次放学后偶然看到了学校游泳池边的园子，对她一见钟情。也不管自己是个旱鸭子，阿薰当即加入了游泳
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="笨金鱼" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E7%AC%A8%E9%87%91%E9%B1%BC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>梦</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-meng/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-meng/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:38:30.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:38:31.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/ccd395f00e6516256d3058c8679d9004.png" alt=""><br>[梦]简介：</p>
<p>　　本片由8个梦境组成：太阳雨。男孩伫立门楣，因目睹狐狸娶亲，遭母亲斥责，后者称其需剖腹谢罪。男孩提刀，误入密林深处，偶遇一群浓妆艳抹的歌伎；桃园。男孩追寻少女桃花精，穿梯田，入农院，邂逅6位女子，待客之时，却发现有一女子若隐若现……风雪。男孩成年（寺尾聪AkiraTerao饰）在冰雪之地遇困……隧道。全军覆没，仅指挥官幸存，隧道里惊现死亡将士……乌鸦。他在博物馆中欣赏梵高的油画，却意外走进了画中世界……红色富士山。他经历了原子弹爆炸后的逃亡，听着幸存者讲述那些放射性物质如何荼毒生灵……鬼泣。他突然被丢到了食人鬼的滩涂，被迫听一个独角鬼诉苦……水车村。葬礼中人们把花朵放在桥上，原来这仪式另有掌故……</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>The film is made up of 8 dreams: the sun and the rain. The boy stood the lintel, witnessed the fox married, was the mother scolded, which said it required laparotomy apology. The boy put a knife into the depths of the forest, and encounters a group of geisha makeup; taoyuan. The boy pursued the maiden peach blossom, wore the terrace, entered the farm, met 6 women, and when he was serving the guests, he found a woman looming…… Blizzard. Boy adult (Temple tail Cong AkiraTerao ornaments) in the ice and snow land trapped…… Tunnel。 The only surviving tunnel, The whole army was wiped out., discovered the death of soldiers…… Crow。 He admired Van Gogh’s painting in the museum, but unexpectedly walked into the painting world…… Red Mt Fuji. He experienced the atomic bomb survivors fled, listen about those radioactive substances to anymore…… Devil may cry. He was suddenly thrown into a cannibal beach and was forced to listen to a unicorn…… Waterwheel village. The funeral people put flowers on the bridge, the ceremony and anecdotes……</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1299112/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1299112/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:A6B30879806BD022A6DB278FB1F86D6225ED9CD1" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:A6B30879806BD022A6DB278FB1F86D6225ED9CD1</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:881F4CC011DA1B45FE707A9A30E0024C15941547" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:881F4CC011DA1B45FE707A9A30E0024C15941547</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:4E5FC4B39EB48A7BC411429B11182209429B158E" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:4E5FC4B39EB48A7BC411429B11182209429B158E</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:FDC4C8421E3216348E6005A7117DF506EC7CEACC" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:FDC4C8421E3216348E6005A7117DF506EC7CEACC</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:E4943A4696E7144377D81E4F38AF99D117471224" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:E4943A4696E7144377D81E4F38AF99D117471224</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/ccd395f00e6516256d3058c8679d9004.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[梦]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　本片由8个梦境组成：太阳雨。男孩伫立门楣，因目睹狐狸娶亲，遭母亲斥责，后者称其需剖腹谢罪。男孩提刀，误入密林深
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="梦" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%A2%A6/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>死之棘</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-si-zhi-ji/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-si-zhi-ji/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:38:19.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:38:19.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/55baa9f9f524596b46c3fa0f4f09eb96.png" alt=""><br>[死之棘]简介：</p>
<p>　　片名《死之棘》取自《圣经》中格林多的传记，意为罪过。<br>　　作家俊夫（岸部一德饰）与美穗（松坂庆子饰）的婚姻生活到了第十个年头，危机凸现。俊夫在外有了情人，妻子雇人调查核实，精神受到极大刺激，扬言自杀。俊夫出于对妻子的愧疚，毅然离开情人，决心和妻子儿女找回以往的快乐时光。但事与愿违，美穗由于承受过大的压力患上了精神分裂症，变得不再相信丈夫，时时猜疑，步步紧逼，使俊夫难以固守最后的个人空间。俊夫深知这一切全是自己种下的恶果，也清楚美穗的反常行为缘于极大的痛苦与悲伤，所以即使无法忍受亦坚忍下来。夫妻关系就在互相折磨中渐渐走向边缘……</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>The title “the sting of death” from the “Bible” in Corinth biography, Italy sin.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1401175/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1401175/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8A1B71E4463201AFF405BA0E517701EA40E708A3" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:8A1B71E4463201AFF405BA0E517701EA40E708A3</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5BEE245E50985A0F2DF2D466501D128F78F07139" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:5BEE245E50985A0F2DF2D466501D128F78F07139</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:40A9B06CC9B1325FA650EA3573CCDFF93CA9D848" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:40A9B06CC9B1325FA650EA3573CCDFF93CA9D848</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:999B500AB29DB111B1677E4117650B5858799E42" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:999B500AB29DB111B1677E4117650B5858799E42</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C4AE944AEE0E05F4D6DBA9C861707DD14686AB76" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:C4AE944AEE0E05F4D6DBA9C861707DD14686AB76</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/55baa9f9f524596b46c3fa0f4f09eb96.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[死之棘]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　片名《死之棘》取自《圣经》中格林多的传记，意为罪过。&lt;br&gt;　　作家俊夫（岸部一德饰）与美穗（松坂庆子饰）
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="死之棘" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%AD%BB%E4%B9%8B%E6%A3%98/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>樱之园</title>
    <link href="http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ying-zhi-yuan/"/>
    <id>http://yuge8.com/201707/1499-ying-zhi-yuan/</id>
    <published>2017-07-03T17:38:06.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-03T17:38:07.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/image/bb212ef8f02195c978a8f5db61d67446.png" alt=""><br>[樱之园]简介：</p>
<p>　　1990年日本电影旬报最佳电影奖。影片通过一所大学的话剧社排演契科夫的同名戏剧，仅用了屈指可数的场景记录了社团成员的生活点滴。<br>　　私立樱华女子学园在每年四月校庆那天，都要上演契柯夫的话剧《樱桃园》，这已成为传统惯例。校庆那天的早晨，演员们都来到演出休息室。在她们中间，最引人注目的就是那天恰好十八岁、第一次烫了头发的队长志水由布子。这些天真烂漫的少女们正在议论三年级学生、扮演男仆亚夏的杉山纪子昨天因吸烟被老师逮住的事。大家忐忑不安地猜测演出是否还会按时进行。在演出顾问里见老师的劝说下，大家的情绪才安定下来。在舞台监督城丸香织的指挥下，准备工作紧张地开始。主要演员仓田知世子由于第一次扮演这个角色，缺少自信，紧张地不能自持。对她一直很崇拜的志水由布子亲切地鼓励着。看到这一切的杉山纪子表现出一种复杂的情绪。演出终于开始了，大幕徐徐拉起，少女们迈着沉着的步伐走向舞台。</p>
<p>[译文]：<br>In 1990 the Japanese film Xunbao Award for best film. The film by a university drama rehearsal Chekhov play of the same name, with only a handful of scenes recorded the life of members of the association.</p>
<p><em>以下资源收集于网络，版权归原资源地所有，下载后请在24小时内删除，勿非法使用！<br>若有资源失效或错误请在下方留言，留言只支持http需手动删除URL中的https访问</em></p>
<p><hr>豆瓣：<a href="http://movie.douban.com/subject/1800608/" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">http://movie.douban.com/subject/1800608/</font></a><hr><br>BT种子(复制链接粘贴到迅雷)：<br><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F45CFF7EA0616146ED32D6F0678751259FD9E7C4" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F45CFF7EA0616146ED32D6F0678751259FD9E7C4</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F3B6F1A3D518C412DDF3A27C20C40C81929B9094" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:F3B6F1A3D518C412DDF3A27C20C40C81929B9094</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1103CF74C8A536D2DD71A45CFC82A22B8E28870B" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1103CF74C8A536D2DD71A45CFC82A22B8E28870B</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1C319B5B4A81EC8E11AA32A9C9F943E6D1D70D8C" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:1C319B5B4A81EC8E11AA32A9C9F943E6D1D70D8C</font></a></p>
<p><hr><a href="magnet:?xt=urn:btih:EEE15C5DF04184845F186850207114A05CA83244" target="_blank" rel="external"><font color="#1e92fb">magnet:?xt=urn:btih:EEE15C5DF04184845F186850207114A05CA83244</font></a></p>
<p><hr><br>百度网盘：</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/image/bb212ef8f02195c978a8f5db61d67446.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;[樱之园]简介：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　1990年日本电影旬报最佳电影奖。影片通过一所大学的话剧社排演契科夫的同名戏剧，仅用了屈指可数的场景记录了
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="电影资源" scheme="http://yuge8.com/categories/%E7%94%B5%E5%BD%B1%E8%B5%84%E6%BA%90/"/>
    
    
      <category term="樱之园" scheme="http://yuge8.com/tags/%E6%A8%B1%E4%B9%8B%E5%9B%AD/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
